<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Bridget Maddison CBT</title>
    <link>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Bridget Maddison CBT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CBT, ACT, and Mindfulness</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/more-about-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/more-about-act/</guid>
      <description>More about CBT Cognitive and Behavioural Therapy (CBT) is a scientifically proven talking therapy that can help people with a wide range of difficulties. It is recommended in the NICE guidelines (National Institute for Clinical Excellence) as an effective treatment for Anxiety based problems and Depression. CBT explores how your thoughts, beliefs and attitudes impacts on what you do and feel and how a greater understanding of these cycles and processes can lead you towards solutions and change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming to therapy</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/coming-to-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/coming-to-therapy/</guid>
      <description>I believe that asking for help takes a lot of courage and can be a daunting prospect, so let me tell you a little more of what to expect should you decide to get in touch. Firstly we can arrange a free initial consultation, by phone at a mutually agreed time.(or via message or email if you prefer) This will give me a broad understanding of what you want to work on and whether I can help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About you</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-you/</guid>
      <description>About you and the problems you may be experiencing.
My training and experience is in working with people from 16 upwards.
Cognitive Behavioural Therapy has been recommended in the NICE Guidelines, (The National Institute for Health and Clinical Excellence) for the following:
 Depression Obsessive Compulsive Disorder (OCD) Panic Phobia Health Anxiety Social Anxiety Generalised Anxiety Disorder or Excessive Worry Post Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD)  I am experienced and trained in the individual evidence based protocols for each of these problems and this informs my practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Referrals I accept referrals from: individuals, GPs, Psychiatrists, Bupa, Vitality Health, Aviva, Nuffield Health, and others.
Current I am an experienced and Accredited (BABCP) Cognitive Behavioural Psychotherapist and Registered Mental Health Nurse. I have been privileged to work with many people, empowering them to gain the skills and strategies required to work through their problems using the CBT model. Research shows that the success of any Therapy experience is very much dependent on the quality of the therapeutic relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My commitment to you</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/my-commitment-to-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/my-commitment-to-you/</guid>
      <description>I have an Enhanced DBS Status (Disclosure and Barring Service, formerly CRB Criminal Record Bureau Check). This is renewed annually.
Professional Bodies I will uphold the requirements of Accreditation by the British Association of Cognitive and Behavioural Psychotherapists (BABCP) and Registration by the Nursing and Midwifery Council (NMC). This requires my commitment to regular attendance of ongoing professional development courses and accessing regular Clinical Supervision.
Confidentiality I guarantee our sessions will remain strictly private and confidential in line with the ethical standards of the BABCP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful links</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/useful-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/useful-links/</guid>
      <description>Online resources  What is CBT (MIND) ACT Mindfully. This is a website from Russ Harris, the author of The Happniess Trap (a popular self-help book). You can download the first 2 chapters of this book for free. Embracing Your Demons: An Overview of Acceptance and Commitment Therapy. The Compassionate Mind Foundation. Compassionate focused audio and video available. Headspace Take 10. Mindfulness app, 10 days of mindfulness for free. Mrs Mindfulness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/contact/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for taking the time to read through these pages, if you think I may be the right person to help you with your difficulties, please contact me now, to arrange a brief informal chat at a mutually agreed time. This will give me a broad understanding of what you want to work on and whether I can help. It will also give you the opportunity to ask any questions and get a sense of whether you feel we can work together before committing to your first appointment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wellbeing Therapy Workshop</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/wellbeing-therapy-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 14:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/wellbeing-therapy-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Using Values, Mindfulness and Self Compassion to build a healthier, happier you.
This is an 8 week programme underpinned by Acceptance and Commitment Therapy or ACT.
We mostly know HOW to improve wellbeing but it can be so difficult to start or sustain changes that would make a difference to our lives. This workshop will:
 give you the tools to manage what gets in the way of looking after you Train you to harness your values as a motivator and to access your &amp;lsquo;Kind Companion&amp;rsquo; to be your coach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wellbeing Therapy Workshop: More Info</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/wellbeing-therapy-workshop-more-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 14:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/wellbeing-therapy-workshop-more-info/</guid>
      <description>Most of us know the changes we want to make to be our healthier selves but we often struggle to do things differently.
Over the 8 weeks, this workshop will enable you to understand why this is the case. We start with an informed and yet compassionate understanding of how our modern world environment works against us. Learn about the basic needs of the ‘cooperative primate’ and find ways to build patterns of practice that you can integrate into your daily life that will meet your ‘monkey needs’!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About this site</title>
      <link>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-this-site/</guid>
      <description>This site is generated using Hugo and makes use of a modified version of the Type theme.
The picture of the Malverns on the front page is a cropped version of a photo taken by Tom Gough and is licensed under CC-BY-SA-2.0.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
