<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bridget Maddison CBT</title>
    <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bridget Maddison CBT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 14:04:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Wellbeing Therapy Workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/wellbeing-therapy-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 14:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/wellbeing-therapy-workshop/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Using Values, Mindfulness and Self Compassion to build a healthier, happier you.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an 8 week programme underpinned by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/more-about-act/&#34;&gt;Acceptance and Commitment Therapy&lt;/a&gt;
or ACT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We mostly know &lt;strong&gt;HOW&lt;/strong&gt; to improve wellbeing but it can be so difficult to
start or sustain changes that would make a difference to our lives. This
workshop will:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;give you the tools to manage what gets in the way of looking after you&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Train you to harness your values as a motivator and to access your &amp;lsquo;Kind
Companion&amp;rsquo; to be your coach.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical skills - mindfulness and compassion based exercises every
session - change from the inside out!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When we approach life in this way we are more able to handle stress, boost
our mood and feel more confident&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is a small steps approach, about integrating healthy practices into your
day to day life, chosen from a Wellbeing Menu&lt;/strong&gt; (From original idea by Professor
Kelly Wilson Co-Founder of ACT).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-wellbeing-menu&#34;&gt;The Wellbeing Menu&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../img/wellbeing-menu.jpg&#34; style=&#34;width: 500px; height: auto; display: block; margin: 0 auto;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eat real food&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move your body&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give yourself sleep and rest opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimise exposure to toxins (physical and social)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage in Meaningful Activity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practice Mindfulness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultivate your Social Network&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultivate Self Compassion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am passionate about  Acceptance and Commitment Therapy, having seen the real
difference it can make to people&amp;rsquo;s lives and have over 3 years experience of
devising and Facilitating an ACT Group Programme within the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;when-and-where&#34;&gt;When and Where?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday evenings beginning on &lt;strong&gt;21st January, 6-8pm&lt;/strong&gt; at
&lt;strong&gt;St Peter&amp;rsquo;s Baptist Church&lt;/strong&gt;, St Peters Worcester WR5 3TZ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday mornings beginning on &lt;strong&gt;6th February 9.30-11.30am&lt;/strong&gt; at &lt;strong&gt;The Beacon
Clinic&lt;/strong&gt;, Malvern WR14 2TA&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost: £165.00&lt;/strong&gt; for 8 Sessions (Introductory cost, usual £185).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secure your place with a £30 deposit (refundable if you are unable to attend), with payment in full due the day before the course begins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email or phone to find out more and secure your place: 07752 199 258 or
contact@bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk. Alternatively, use my &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/contact/&#34;&gt;contact form&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will send you an online Payment link (Paypal invoice).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;more-info&#34;&gt;More info&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/wellbeing-therapy-workshop-more-info/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for more
information about the programme.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wellbeing Therapy Workshop: More Info</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/wellbeing-therapy-workshop-more-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 14:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/wellbeing-therapy-workshop-more-info/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Most of us know the changes we want to make to be our healthier selves but we often struggle to do things differently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the 8 weeks, this workshop will enable you to understand why this is the
case. We start with an informed and yet compassionate understanding of how our
modern world environment works against us. Learn about the basic needs of the
‘cooperative primate’ and find ways to build patterns of practice that you can
integrate into your daily life that will meet your ‘monkey needs’!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This workshop is designed to problem solve our finite resources of time,
finance, energy…. these are things that we need to build changes around. The
emphasis is on identifying and integrating small workable actions that can
build into patterns and hopefully habits. This approach sees ‘failure’ as part
of the learning process, providing opportunities to notice what happened and
get ready with awareness for next time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personalise your steps for change with your ‘Wellbeing Matrix’ - an awareness
tool, that trains you to bring you Values into your day to day experience and
become more alert to  what shows up and gets in the way of you doing the
things that would make life better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We use Metaphor  to see things more clearly and promote change. Consider your
‘Wellbeing Garden’, which bits are being neglected, what are the ‘birds’ that
swoop down and stop new growth?!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The workshops are practical and each session involves mindfulness based
exercises so you can notice your ‘chattering mind’ and become more open to
feelings or sensations that might want to take you off track from you pathway
to wellbeing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We draw on the brain science of Compassion and how taking the perspective of
the Kindly Companion means we can more effectively coach ourselves through the
tricky times and celebrate!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Wellbeing Menu enables you personalise the group experience as you choose
where to focus your attention but also promotes a holistic approach to
wellbeing -  creating the conditions for feeling better thus more likely to
withstand life’s ups and downs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commit to weekly tasks to build patterns of change and log to share with group
members. Every session includes a ‘Pattern Builder’ - one small change to
integrate into your week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary-of-the-8-sessions&#34;&gt;Summary of the 8 Sessions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../img/wellbeing-summary.jpg&#34; style=&#34;width: 500px; height: auto; display: block; margin: 0 auto;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session 1&lt;/strong&gt;: Introductions, The Wellbeing Menu, The modern world habitat, The survival brain, Identifying your ‘fix it’ strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session 2&lt;/strong&gt;: Devise your own Wellbeing Matrix - Trains you to: notice, sort and choose - what is helpful and healthy as well as what gets in the way of this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session 3&lt;/strong&gt;: Introducing Mindfulness skills - wake up out of autopilot, connect to your 5 senses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session 4&lt;/strong&gt;: Respond more flexibly to  thoughts and feelings that send you off track - getting curious - responding not reacting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session 5&lt;/strong&gt;: The brain science of Compassion - the ‘Kindly Companion’ - coaching with courage!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session 6&lt;/strong&gt;: What Matters - using values as your compass and motivator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session 7&lt;/strong&gt;: From Values to action - Building Patterns from the Wellbeing Menu and trouble-shooting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session 8&lt;/strong&gt;: My Wellbeing Plan. Building resilience and going forwards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All sessions include Pattern Builders - or ways to integrate small steps
from the Wellbeing menu into your week.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sign-up&#34;&gt;Sign up&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/wellbeing-therapy-workshop/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for details dates,
times, and how to register.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About this site</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-this-site/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This site is generated using &lt;a href=&#34;http://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; and makes use of a
modified version of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/digitalcraftsman/hugo-type-theme&#34;&gt;Type
theme&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The picture of the Malverns on the front page is a cropped version of a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/45072550@N03/6026720060/&#34;&gt;photo
taken by Tom Gough&lt;/a&gt;
and is &lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.0/&#34;&gt;licensed under
CC-BY-SA-2.0&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More about CBT and ACT</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/more-about-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/more-about-act/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/img/change_clouds.jpg&#34; style=&#34;width: 60%; height: auto; 
background-size: cover;&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;more-about-cbt&#34;&gt;More about CBT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cognitive and Behavioural Therapy (CBT)&lt;/strong&gt; is a scientifically proven
talking therapy that can help people with a wide range of difficulties. It is
recommended in the NICE guidelines (National Institute for Clinical
Excellence) as an effective treatment for Anxiety based problems and
Depression. CBT explores how your thoughts, beliefs and attitudes
impacts on what you do and feel and how a greater understanding of
these cycles and processes can lead you towards solutions and change.
CBT tends to be more focused on the present but can refer to the past to
better understand how it impacts on the here and now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Third wave family of Cognitive Behavioural Therapies includes
Acceptance and Commitment Therapy or ACT and Compassion
Focused Therapy (amongst others). I am able to draw from this
innovative body of knowledge with its growing evidence base to ensure
you get a tailor-made therapy suited to your particular needs. ACT uses
Mindfulness and Acceptance skills to help you negotiate what gets in the
way of what matters to you, whilst Compassion Focused Therapy has a
focus on responding kindly and wisely to the inner critic and painful
feelings.
I hope you choose to read further but in essence, CBT is really about
becoming your own inner coach and brain trainer! so you can do more of
what’s healthy and helpful in your life and less of the things that aren’t
working. Find out more about the problems that can be effectively treated
with CBT under &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-you/&#34;&gt;About You&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-acceptance-and-commitment-therapy&#34;&gt;What is Acceptance and Commitment Therapy?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/img/acthands.jpg&#34; style=&#34;width: 40%; height: auto; background-size: cover;&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Acceptance and Commitment Therapy gets its name from its main themes&lt;/strong&gt; - to
accept things that are out of your control and commit to changing things
that can be changed to make your life better. In summary, ACT uses
mindfulness and acceptance skills to develop a more flexible relationship
with your thoughts, feelings, memories and sensations. Time is also taken
to clarify what gives your life meaning, your values. Without being held
back by tricky thoughts and feelings and with a new sense of purpose and
direction, you can begin to build a more enriched and meaningful life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acceptance and Commitment Therapy (say Act, not A.C.T.!) is an engaging and
playful approach to tackling life&amp;rsquo;s difficulties. Just like traditional
Cognitive Behavioural Therapy, it is underpinned by a growing body of
scientific evidence highlighting its effectiveness for many psychological
problems and challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ACT draws on brain science&lt;/strong&gt; to show we are all wired to &amp;lsquo;suffer&amp;rsquo; or find
life difficult because we are designed to pay attention to anything we
perceive as threat. This explains why we often find ourselves caught up in
our in our &amp;lsquo;chattering&amp;rsquo; mind, over-thinking ourselves, our problems or
disturbed by our feelings. We are also programmed to find solutions, to
deal with the &amp;lsquo;threat&amp;rsquo;, (in this case our thoughts and feelings), so we are
naturally compelled to distract ourselves from this tricky stuff or avoid
things that lead them to show up in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This gets us caught up in unhelpful vicious cycles&lt;/strong&gt;, like comfort eating,
relying on alcohol, retail therapy, spending too long watching shows,
checking social media, sleeping or overworking&amp;hellip; the list is long! In Act we
call this, &lt;strong&gt;The Struggle&lt;/strong&gt;, when in an effort not to feel or think we end up
doing things or not doing things that take us away from the person we want
to be or the life we want to lead. (Clearly most of these things are fine
in moderation!). These ineffective coping strategies often play a key part
in maintaining things like anxiety, depression and low self esteem and may
cost us dearly in terms of time, energy, money, health and relationships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-does-it-help&#34;&gt;How does it help?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The research underpinning Acceptance and Commitment Therapy shows that we
are also pre-programmed with the capacity to develop skills to work through
life&amp;rsquo;s challenges - there is hope! In sessions you will &lt;strong&gt;learn key skills&lt;/strong&gt; to
enable you to step back from your chattering mind and what may be at times
toxic thinking and learn ways to have and handle uncomfortable or painful
feelings. Through mindfulness and acceptance skills, use of metaphor,
experiential exercises and the development of self compassion, we will
actively construct a new way for you to respond to long-standing habits and
reactions that you know are not helping. If your life has grown narrower,
we will draw on tried and tested behavioural strategies such as Graded
Exposure and Behavioural Activation to enable you to move TOWARDS things
you may have been avoiding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These skills help promote what ACT refers to as &lt;strong&gt;PSYCHOLOGICAL FLEXIBILITY&lt;/strong&gt;,
which is all about trying to build a new relationship with difficult
thoughts, feelings and sensations, one that doesn&amp;rsquo;t rely on avoidance or
distraction. In essence, this means we are less stressed/distressed and
able to do more of what we value, giving us a greater sense of meaning,
purpose and therefore, well-being&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;change-or-connecting-to-what-matters&#34;&gt;Change or connecting to what matters&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If battling with our difficulties pulls us away from how we want our lives
to be then getting things on track needs to take into account our &amp;lsquo;bigger
picture&amp;rsquo; – what is important to us in life. Taking time to identify your
values will enable you to set meaningful goals, giving you a greater sense
of purpose and can become a motivator when things are tricky. From my
experience this work also helps people appreciate what they already have in
their lives right now. ACT is also a really practical therapy of change so
if moving forward involves learning new skills or solving problems we can
consider this too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-compassion-focused-therapy&#34;&gt;What is Compassion Focused Therapy?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compassion-focused therapy (CFT) aims to help promote mental and
emotional healing by encouraging people in treatment to be
compassionate toward themselves and other people. It is another
member of the wider family of Cognitive Behavioural Therapies and was
founded by Professor Paul Gilbert.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like ACT, CFT emphasises the inherent difficulty of our evolved Tricky
Brains which can make us our own worst critic. Compassion Focused
Therapy is particularly relevant to those who experience feelings of
shame or guilt and self-critical thinking. Many people feel able to
respond in a kindly and supportive fashion to others but struggle to
motivate themselves in this way. Although the word Compassion makes
us think of qualities like kindness and warmth, this approach also places
great emphasis on the strength and courage it takes to engage with our
suffering and do something about it. CFT presents Compassion as a skill
that can be developed and nurtured through Compassionate Focused
Exercises and Practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-mindfulness&#34;&gt;What is Mindfulness&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ever noticed how you get caught up in your head, thinking about the
next thing to do, worrying or re-living the past. Experts say we spend up
to 47% of our waking moments in autopilot! Mindfulness is a way of
training your mind to be more aware of the here and now so we can
actually live life in the present. It enables us to hold attention where we
choose, rather than what our thoughts or feelings dictate. Its aim is not
to try and control or suppress our thoughts or distract from our feelings
but to enable us to see them for what they are – mental events. Learning
to look at our thoughts rather than from them means we no longer have
to over identify with what our mind is telling us. If we can learn to notice
our experiences, take a step back, we are freed to choose how we want
to respond. This increases the likelihood that we can start acting in ways
that are more healthy and helpful and move us towards a better life.
Finally, Mindfulness enables us to be more present in those moments
that really matter, so we can appreciate them in all their glory rather than
being &amp;ldquo;there but not there&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Therapist I’m a great believer in &amp;ldquo;practice what you preach&amp;rdquo; so do
my best to commit to a daily mindfulness practice. I hope this increases
my own capacity to be open, present and aware within a Therapy
Session.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming to therapy</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/coming-to-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/coming-to-therapy/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;I believe that asking for help takes a lot of courage and can be a daunting
prospect, so let me tell you a little more of what to expect should you decide
to get in touch. Firstly we can arrange a free initial consultation, by phone
at a mutually agreed time.(or via message or email if you prefer) This will
give me a broad understanding of what you want to work on and whether I can
help. It will also give you the opportunity to ask any questions and get a
sense of whether you feel we can work together before committing to your first
appointment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research shows that the success of any therapy experience is very much related
to the quality of the therapeutic relationship and I believe I bring a non
judgemental, warm and kindly approach to sessions, infused with a little
humour!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many sessions you need to come for very much depends on your problem and
what you&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to work on.  CBT is not a quick fix approach, though
relatively short term and Nice Guidelines usually advise between 6 and 16
sessions, with attendance on a weekly basis. It isn&amp;rsquo;t unusual for people to
come for a course of CBT and then return a year or so later for booster
sessions to reinforce or develop previous learning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CBT is very much a collaborative approach, so the first stage of therapy is to
develop a shared understanding of your problem.  The first couple of sessions
will usually involve developing an overview of what is problematic in terms of
thoughts, feelings and behaviour, identifying vicious cycles, as well as a
consideration of the roots of the problem, how the past informs the present.
We can then map out a tailor made Treatment Plan, based on your hopes for
therapy and what is realistic within the agreed time frame. CBT is a proactive
therapy so further sessions will involve you learning skills and strategies
alongside values based goal setting and problem solving.  You will be supported
in actively practising these skills between sessions ready for further
reflection and fine tuning when you return. CBT is all about coaching people to
become their own therapist, so towards the end of therapy we will develop a
plan for handling setbacks and promoting emotional resilience. My nursing
background enables me to offer an holistic approach to your difficulties,
taking into account physical health conditions and the role of medications
prescribed for mood management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;terms-of-business&#34;&gt;Terms of business&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;fees&#34;&gt;Fees&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Initial consultation - brief phone-call, message, email: No charge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;£65 per Therapy Hour (55 mins) face to face, 5 minutes for endings, payment,
rebooking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To be paid at end of session&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sessions funded by Health Insurance Companies may be subject to a
different fee as agreed with individual organisations.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Method of Payment&lt;/strong&gt;: Credit or Debit Card (via card reader), Cheque, (made
payable to Bridget Maddison), Cash, Bank Transfer, Paypal Invoice via email (you
don&amp;rsquo;t need a Paypal account for this).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;missed-or-cancelled-appointments&#34;&gt;Missed or cancelled appointments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please to get in touch as soon as possible if you are unable to attend, so I can offer
the slot to someone else. For less than 24 hours notice I would ask you to pay 50%
of the session fee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;late-arrival&#34;&gt;Late arrival&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you come late to session, I may not be able to see you for longer to make up the
time, so we might need to have a shorter session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;testimonials&#34;&gt;Testimonials&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I contacted Bridget after experiencing moments of anxiety at work, my doctor
mentioned that Cognitive Behavioural Therapy could be really useful - it
certainly is! I found Bridget’s approach very understanding and proactive. I
feel I know much more about myself, how the brain operates and how we can work
together more effectively. I believe I have acquired life skill which I will
continue to develop.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;2018&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I would highly recommend Bridget to anyone considering CBT counselling. She 
has really helped me to better understand myself and has given me a virtual 
bag of tools with which to move forward with confidence and choose how to be.
Her manner is very supportive and non- judgemental and I found it very easy to 
understand the concepts and incorporate
them into daily life. If, as they say, life is a journey, my experience with 
Bridget was like picking up a map and a compass after storms had beaten me 
down. It doesn&#39;t change the weather or the boat you are in, but you have some 
tools to allow you to choose how get you where, and how, you would like to 
be.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;March 2017&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
Having suffered with OCD for 20 years I sought Cognitive Behavioural Therapy 
and Bridget came into my life as a blessing! She handled my situation with 
great care and empathy and used her extensive skills to teach me and guide me 
into dealing with my OCD and learning how to free myself from some of the 
debilitating symptoms that it causes. Bridget is professional and thorough and 
puts everything into helping you to heal yourself. She is compassionate yet 
tough when she knows that you need to be tough! She has given me tools &amp; 
skills that enabled me to get my life back. She is incredible! If you need 
her, go and see her, you will be so thankful you did!
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lucy, Worcestershire&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I want to thank you for the time that you have given to me over the last
months.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
This is the first time that I have needed professional help. When I first came
to you I could not envisage a positive outcome or a time when I would be able
to return to my old self.  However, thanks to your wise counsel,  vision,
support and teaching I now have many new skills developed during our CBT
sessions that I use daily. I  truly believe that I will not be returning to my
old self but in fact a new, better and more fulfilled self.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Bridget, my family and I are eternally grateful to you for our time together.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;June 2016&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About you</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About you and the problems you may be experiencing.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My training and experience is in working with people from 16 upwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cognitive Behavioural Therapy has been recommended in the NICE Guidelines, (The National Institute for Health and Clinical Excellence) for the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Depression&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Obsessive Compulsive Disorder (OCD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Panic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phobia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health Anxiety&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Anxiety&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generalised Anxiety Disorder or Excessive Worry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am experienced and trained in the individual evidence based protocols for each of these problems and this informs my practice. However, my experience of real people tells me that few people actually fit into these neat boxes and a broader or ‘transdiagnostic’ approach can be beneficial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a strong interest and considerable experience in the following areas
for which an ACT approach has been found to be particularly beneficial:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping people manage their emotions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing Stress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing long term conditions eg Chronic Fatigue or Multiple Sclerosis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building Self Acceptance  to boost Self Esteem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mood difficulties following bereavement of loved ones or pets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Binge Eating&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shyness or social difficulties relating to autistic spectrum disorder traits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coming to terms with change, for example, following divorce or retirement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also enjoy working with people who just need someone to help them step back,
take stock and reconnect with their values.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever your problem, your treatment plan will be tailor-made to suit your
individual needs. We will also have regular reviews to ensure skills and
strategies being learned and practised continue to fit with your planned hopes
for change.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-me/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;referrals&#34;&gt;Referrals&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I accept referrals from: individuals, GPs, Psychiatrists,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://finder.bupa.co.uk/Consultant/view/215281/mrs_bridget_maddison&#34;&gt;Bupa&lt;/a&gt;, Vitality
Health, Aviva, Nuffield Health, and others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;current&#34;&gt;Current&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am an experienced and Accredited (BABCP) Cognitive Behavioural
Psychotherapist and Registered Mental Health Nurse. I have been privileged to
work with many people, empowering them to gain the skills and strategies required
to work through their problems using the CBT model. Research shows that the
success of any Therapy experience is very much dependent on the quality of the
therapeutic relationship. I believe I bring a non-judgemental, warm and kindly
approach to sessions, ensuring you feel safe and supported as we work together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have 15 years of experience of working within the NHS, completing my Post
Graduate Qualification in CBT in 2010. Alongside my individual work with Clients I
have enjoyed devising and facilitating an Acceptance and Commitment Therapy
Group Programme (ACT) which continues to run across the County.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following my decision to leave the NHS in 2018 I will work solely from the Beacon
Clinic from 2019 with individuals from 16 upwards and also offer a Group Therapy Programme - A
Wellbeing Therapy Workshop from the Beacon Clinic and in Worcester.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have experience of providing Clinical Supervision within the NHS and externally. I
currently offer Supervision for those interested in building skills within the ACT Model.
This can be face to face or on Skype or Zoom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;qualifications&#34;&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post Graduate Diploma in Cognitive and Behavioural Therapy, University Of Birmingham
2010&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diploma of Higher Education (Nursing) Part 13 of Register RMN (Distinction)
Pin No. 00E0415E, 2003&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor of Arts (Honours) Open University 1998&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;experience&#34;&gt;Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2003: Following completion of my Mental Health Nursing Diploma, I worked on
an Acute Psychiatric Ward in Worcester, prior to moving to a Day Hospital
setting, where I worked with people individually and in groups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2006: Joined Primary Care Mental Health Service in Worcestershire as a
Gateway Worker (this involved, mental health reviews, using CBT approach
interventions and signposting for other Services).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2008: Completed Postgraduate Diploma in CBT at the University of Birmingham.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2011: Full Accreditation with BABCP (British Association for Cognitive and Behavioural Psychotherapists)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2010-2018: CBT Therapist within Worcestershire Healthy Minds, providing
individual Therapy, Clinical Supervision and Group work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018 (December): Left the NHS to focus on Private Practice (individual work with Clients, Group Therapy)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;code-of-ethics-and-regulation&#34;&gt;Code of Ethics and Regulation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a continuing commitment to best practice and regularly attend workshops and
Courses which support my professional development and contribute to my ongoing
Accreditation and Registration. I receive regular Supervision, from a BABCP
Accredited Clinical Psychologist and Peer Reviewed ACT Trainer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an Accredited member of the British Association of Behavioural and Cognitive
Therapists and the Nursing and Midwifery Council, my work is underpinned by the
Professional Standards of Conduct and Ethics outlined by these established
organisations. I am also a member of the Association for Contextual and Behavioural
Scientists, which enables me to develop my practice within the ACT model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have an Enhanced Disclosure and Barring Service Status&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My commitment to you</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/my-commitment-to-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/my-commitment-to-you/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;I have an Enhanced DBS Status (Disclosure and Barring Service, formerly CRB
Criminal Record Bureau Check). This is renewed annually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;professional-bodies&#34;&gt;Professional Bodies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will uphold the requirements of Accreditation by the British Association of
Cognitive and Behavioural Psychotherapists (BABCP) and Registration by the
Nursing and Midwifery Council (NMC). This requires my commitment to regular
attendance of ongoing professional development courses and accessing regular
Clinical Supervision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;confidentiality&#34;&gt;Confidentiality&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guarantee our sessions will remain strictly private and confidential in line
with the ethical standards of the BABCP.  The only  exception to this would be
if you tell me something that makes me very concerned about your safety or the
safety of someone else. In that case, I would have gained your agreement in the
first session to share my concerns with a designated family member or
Professional. This would usually be a step we would plan together to enable you
to access the further help you need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To improve my Service to you and as part of the requirements of my Professional
Body, I may review our sessions with my Clinical Supervisor. Your anonymity
will be maintained throughout and the Supervisor is also bound to keep your
information confidential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;data-storage&#34;&gt;Data Storage&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will store your data electronically and make use of two-factor authentication
for all services involved in storing your data. I am a registered Data
Controller under the Data Protection Act 1998 and I
operate in accordance with its legal requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;insurance&#34;&gt;Insurance&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hold Professional Insurance (professional indemnity and public liability).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful links</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/useful-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/useful-links/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;online-resources&#34;&gt;Online resources&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mind.org.uk/information-support/drugs-and-treatments/cognitive-behavioural-therapy-cbt/#.VttCEFuLSVM&#34;&gt;What is CBT
(MIND)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.actmindfully.com.au/free_resources&#34;&gt;ACT Mindfully&lt;/a&gt;. This is a
website from Russ Harris, the author of The Happniess Trap (a popular
self-help book). You can download the first 2 chapters of this book
for free.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.actmindfully.com.au/upimages/Dr_Russ_Harris_-_A_Non-technical_Overview_of_ACT.pdf&#34;&gt;Embracing Your Demons: An Overview of Acceptance and Commitment Therapy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://compassionatemind.co.uk/&#34;&gt;The Compassionate Mind Foundation&lt;/a&gt;.
Compassionate focused audio and video available.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.headspace.com&#34;&gt;Headspace Take 10&lt;/a&gt;. Mindfulness app, 10 days of
mindfulness for free.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://mrsmindfulness.com/&#34;&gt;Mrs Mindfulness&lt;/a&gt;. Australian-based mindfulness
website by Melli O&amp;rsquo;Brien.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://franticworld.com/free-meditations-from-mindfulness/&#34;&gt;Free meditations from
Mindfulness&lt;/a&gt;. Free
mindfulness audio to download by Mark Williams and Danny Penman&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;videos&#34;&gt;Videos&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;videos-about-our-tricky-minds&#34;&gt;Videos about our tricky minds&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C-ZuqeyxULM&#34;&gt;Headstuck! What is Experiential
Avoidance?&lt;/a&gt;. This short animation
provides a great introduction to some key concepts underlying Acceptance and
Commitment Therapy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rCp1l16GCXI&#34;&gt;The Struggle Switch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dz_nexLqY_8&#34;&gt;Internal Struggles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=93LFNtcR1Ok&#34;&gt;The 3 Happiness Myths&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eiPxLpYlw4I&#34;&gt;The Values-Focused vs the Goals-Focused
Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bSpPgL3VaHI&#34;&gt;The Choice Point&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o79_gmO5ppg&#34;&gt;Psychological flexibility: How love turns pain into purpose&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kv6HkipQcfA&#34;&gt;The Happiness Trap: Evolution of the Human Mind&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OV15x8LvwAQ&#34;&gt;The Choice Point: A Map for a Meaningful Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=206WtwEyqzg&#34;&gt;Thanking Your Mind: Taking The Power Out of Difficult Thoughts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ted.com/talks/susan_david_the_gift_and_power_of_emotional_courage&#34;&gt;Susan David: The gift and power of emotional courage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ted.com/talks/brene_brown_on_vulnerability&#34;&gt;Brené Brown: The power of vulnerability&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ted.com/talks/thandie_newton_embracing_otherness_embracing_myself&#34;&gt;Thandie Newton: Embracing otherness, embracing myself&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z-wyaP6xXwE&#34;&gt;Demons on the Boat Metaphor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z29ptSuoWRc&#34;&gt;Passengers on a Bus Metaphore&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tzUoXJVI0wo&#34;&gt;Sushi Train Metaphor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VExjWHx2R1E&#34;&gt;Russ Harris: The Limbic Brain and its Role in Trauma&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7N9r8nVogM8&#34;&gt;What if my brain held a meeting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XvnEn1Y-gcQ&#34;&gt;Relational frame theory - how language shapes our
experience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VYht-guymF4&#34;&gt;The unwelcome party guest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;self-compassion&#34;&gt;Self compassion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-kfUE41-JFw&#34;&gt;Self Compassion: The School of
Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1Evwgu369Jw&#34;&gt;Brené Brown on Empathy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RZWf2_2L2v8&#34;&gt;Brené Brown on Blame&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;mindfulness&#34;&gt;Mindfulness&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w6T02g5hnT4&#34;&gt;Why Mindfulness is a
Superpower&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://mrsmindfulness.com/what-is-mindfulness/&#34;&gt;An Introduction to
Mindfulness&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HmEo6RI4Wvs&#34;&gt;What is Mindfulness&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=URL5xHCK1-I&#34;&gt;How to Meditate Anytime,
Anywhere&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aNCB1MZDgQA&#34;&gt;Mindfulness and How the Brain
Works&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F0WYFXxhPGY&#34;&gt;Underlying Calm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vzKryaN44ss&#34;&gt;How Mindfulness Empowers Us&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1sgb2cUqFiY&#34;&gt;How to Breathe - Belisa Vranich&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;books&#34;&gt;Books&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Little ACT Workbook - An Introduction to Acceptance and Commitment Therapy&lt;/strong&gt;, Michael
Sinclair and Dr Matthew Beadman, 2016&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Happiness Trap&lt;/strong&gt;, Russ Harris, 2008. A best selling introduction to ACT (also - The
Illustrated Happiness Trap, The Happiness Trap Pocketbook, concise versions of the main text)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Activate your life - Using Acceptance and Mindfulness to build a life that is rich, fulfilling and
fun&lt;/strong&gt;, Joe Oliver, Jon Hill, Eric Morris, 2015. Develop your Open, Aware, and Active skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Living with the Enemy&lt;/strong&gt;, Ray Owen, 2013. Coping with the stress of chronic illness using CBT,
Mindfulness and Acceptance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Mindfulness Guide for the Frazzled&lt;/strong&gt;, Ruby Wax, 2008.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Compassionate Mind Workbook: A step-by-step guide to developing your
compassionate self&lt;/strong&gt;, Chris Irons, 2016&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/contact/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for taking the time to read through these pages, if you think I may be
the right person to help you with your difficulties, please contact me now, to
arrange a brief informal chat at a mutually agreed time. This will give me a
broad understanding of what you want to work on and whether I can help. It will
also give you the opportunity to ask any questions and get a sense of whether
you feel we can work together before committing to your first appointment.
Feel free to call me, or if you prefer email me a summary of your current
problem and we can take it from there. You can also fill out the contact form
below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will endeavour to get back to you as soon as I can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phone: &lt;strong&gt;07752 199258&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:contact@bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk&#34;&gt;contact@bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe 
src=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1nHvkFc7cPkGPb0PiaDYbWHIcL-P60IiLBME4lXQ97ok/viewform?embedded=true&#34; 
width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;500&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; marginheight=&#34;0&#34; 
marginwidth=&#34;0&#34;&gt;Loading...&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of 2019, sessions will take place at the Beacon Clinic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Website:    &lt;a href=&#34;http://beaconclinic.net/&#34;&gt;beaconclinic.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beacon Clinic&lt;br /&gt;
Portland Road&lt;br /&gt;
Great Malvern&lt;br /&gt;
WR14 2TA&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fees:    £65 per Therapy hour (55 mins) Payment by debit/credit card, cash,
cheque, brank transfer, or Paypal invoice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;cancellations-or-non-attendance&#34;&gt;Cancellations or non attendance&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please to get in touch as soon as possible if you are unable to attend. For less than 24 hours notice I would ask you to pay 50% of the session fee.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>