<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bridget Maddison CBT</title>
    <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bridget Maddison CBT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About this site</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-this-site/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This site is generated using &lt;a href=&#34;http://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; and makes use of a
modified version of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/digitalcraftsman/hugo-type-theme&#34;&gt;Type
theme&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The picture of the Malverns on the front page is a cropped version of a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/45072550@N03/6026720060/&#34;&gt;photo
taken by Tom Gough&lt;/a&gt;
and is &lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.0/&#34;&gt;licensed under
CC-BY-SA-2.0&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More about CBT and ACT</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/more-about-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/more-about-act/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/img/change_clouds.jpg&#34; style=&#34;width: 60%; height: auto; 
background-size: cover;&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;more-about-cbt:5b95af52769ff5e43b92455393a21e12&#34;&gt;More about CBT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cognitive and Behavioural Therapy (CBT)&lt;/strong&gt; is a scientifically proven talking
therapy that can help people with a wide range of difficulties. It is
recommended in the NICE guidelines (National Institute for Clinical Excellence)
as an effective treatment for Anxiety based problems and Depression. CBT
explores how your thoughts, beliefs and attitudes impacts on what you do and
feel and how a greater understanding of these cycles and processes can lead you
towards solutions and change. CBT tends to be more focused on the present but
might also look at your past to help you understand how your past impacts on
the present. Find out more about the problems that can be effectively treated
with CBT under &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-you/&#34;&gt;About You&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over recent years I have been increasingly drawn to &lt;strong&gt;Acceptance and Commitment
Therapy (ACT)&lt;/strong&gt;. This falls under the &amp;lsquo;umbrella&amp;rsquo; of CBT and is often referred to
as one of the &amp;lsquo;third wave&amp;rsquo; family of Cognitive Behavioural Therapies. What I
love about ACT and why I&amp;rsquo;ve begun to use it more in my Practice, is that
alongside its growing evidence base and great feedback from patients, I know
how much more prepared I am myself to handle life&amp;rsquo;s challenges, through using
these skills and ideas! It is also particularly helpful when you are
experiencing a number of problems at the same time or your problems are
longstanding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-acceptance-and-commitment-therapy:5b95af52769ff5e43b92455393a21e12&#34;&gt;What is Acceptance and Commitment Therapy?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/img/acthands.jpg&#34; style=&#34;width: 40%; height: auto; background-size: cover;&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Acceptance and Commitment Therapy gets its name from its main themes&lt;/strong&gt; - to
accept things that are out of your control and commit to changing things
that can be changed to make your life better. In summary, ACT uses
mindfulness and acceptance skills to develop a more flexible relationship
with your thoughts, feelings, memories and sensations. Time is also taken
to clarify what gives your life meaning, your values. Without being held
back by tricky thoughts and feelings and with a new sense of purpose and
direction, you can begin to build a more enriched and meaningful life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acceptance and Commitment Therapy (say Act, not A.C.T.!) is an engaging and
playful approach to tackling life&amp;rsquo;s difficulties. Just like traditional
Cognitive Behavioural Therapy, it is underpinned by a growing body of
scientific evidence highlighting its effectiveness for many psychological
problems and challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ACT draws on brain science&lt;/strong&gt; to show we are all wired to &amp;lsquo;suffer&amp;rsquo; or find
life difficult because we are designed to pay attention to anything we
perceive as threat. This explains why we often find ourselves caught up in
our in our &amp;lsquo;chattering&amp;rsquo; mind, over-thinking ourselves, our problems or
disturbed by our feelings. We are also programmed to find solutions, to
deal with the &amp;lsquo;threat&amp;rsquo;, (in this case our thoughts and feelings), so we are
naturally compelled to distract ourselves from this tricky stuff or avoid
things that lead them to show up in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This gets us caught up in unhelpful vicious cycles&lt;/strong&gt;, like comfort eating,
relying on alcohol, retail therapy, spending too long watching shows,
checking social media, sleeping or overworking&amp;hellip; the list is long! In Act we
call this, &lt;strong&gt;The Struggle&lt;/strong&gt;, when in an effort not to feel or think we end up
doing things or not doing things that take us away from the person we want
to be or the life we want to lead. (Clearly most of these things are fine
in moderation!). These ineffective coping strategies often play a key part
in maintaining things like anxiety, depression and low self esteem and may
cost us dearly in terms of time, energy, money, health and relationships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-does-it-help:5b95af52769ff5e43b92455393a21e12&#34;&gt;How does it help?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The research underpinning Acceptance and Commitment Therapy shows that we
are also pre-programmed with the capacity to develop skills to work through
life&amp;rsquo;s challenges - there is hope! In sessions you will &lt;strong&gt;learn key skills&lt;/strong&gt; to
enable you to step back from your chattering mind and what may be at times
toxic thinking and learn ways to have and handle uncomfortable or painful
feelings. Through mindfulness and acceptance skills, use of metaphor,
experiential exercises and the development of self compassion, we will
actively construct a new way for you to respond to long-standing habits and
reactions that you know are not helping. If your life has grown narrower,
we will draw on tried and tested behavioural strategies such as Graded
Exposure and Behavioural Activation to enable you to move TOWARDS things
you may have been avoiding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These skills help promote what ACT refers to as &lt;strong&gt;PSYCHOLOGICAL FLEXIBILITY&lt;/strong&gt;,
which is all about trying to build a new relationship with difficult
thoughts, feelings and sensations, one that doesn&amp;rsquo;t rely on avoidance or
distraction. In essence, this means we are less stressed/distressed and
able to do more of what we value, giving us a greater sense of meaning,
purpose and therefore, well-being&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;change-or-connecting-to-what-matters:5b95af52769ff5e43b92455393a21e12&#34;&gt;Change or connecting to what matters&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If battling with our difficulties pulls us away from how we want our lives
to be then getting things on track needs to take into account our &amp;lsquo;bigger
picture&amp;rsquo; – what is important to us in life. Taking time to identify your
values will enable you to set meaningful goals, giving you a greater sense
of purpose and can become a motivator when things are tricky. From my
experience this work also helps people appreciate what they already have in
their lives right now. ACT is also a really practical therapy of change so
if moving forward involves learning new skills or solving problems we can
consider this too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;mindfulness-and-act:5b95af52769ff5e43b92455393a21e12&#34;&gt;Mindfulness and ACT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a little more information on how mindfulness is used in Acceptance and Commitment Therapy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It tends to be more &amp;lsquo;bite-sized&amp;rsquo; based on research that shows that even brief
periods of regular mindfulness practice (5- 10 mins or just mini mindful
moments!) can still be beneficial and help us to &amp;lsquo;rewire&amp;rsquo; our brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;While many people think mindfulness means meditation, this is not the case.
Mindfulness is a mental state of openness, awareness and focus, and meditation
is just one way amongst hundreds of learning to cultivate this
state.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Russ Harris&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ACT breaks Mindfulness down into 4 key skills:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Defusion - distancing from and letting go of unhelpful thoughts, beliefs,
memories, images, rules for living etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Willingness - making room for painful feelings, urges and sensations, and
allowing them to come and go without a struggle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact with the present moment: engaging fully with our here and now
experience, with an attitude of openness and curiosity. Getting better at being
connected to the here and now and the things we value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Being the Observer of our experience so we are no longer defined by it. Not
caught up in unhelpful stories of ourselves based on our past or our fears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming to therapy</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/coming-to-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/coming-to-therapy/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;I believe that asking for help takes a lot of courage and can be a daunting
prospect, so let me tell you a little more of what to expect should you decide
to get in touch. Firstly we can arrange a free initial consultation, by phone
at a mutually agreed time.(or via message or email if you prefer) This will
give me a broad understanding of what you want to work on and whether I can
help. It will also give you the opportunity to ask any questions and get a
sense of whether you feel we can work together before committing to your first
appointment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research shows that the success of any therapy experience is very much related
to the quality of the therapeutic relationship and I believe I bring a non
judgemental, warm and kindly approach to sessions, infused with a little
humour!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many sessions you need to come for very much depends on your problem and
what you&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to work on.  CBT is not a quick fix approach, though
relatively short term and Nice Guidelines usually advise between 6 and 16
sessions, with attendance on a weekly basis. It isn&amp;rsquo;t unusual for people to
come for a course of CBT and then return a year or so later for booster
sessions to reinforce or develop previous learning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CBT is very much a collaborative approach, so the first stage of therapy is to
develop a shared understanding of your problem.  The first couple of sessions
will usually involve developing an overview of what is problematic in terms of
thoughts, feelings and behaviour, identifying vicious cycles, as well as a
consideration of the roots of the problem, how the past informs the present.
We can then map out a tailor made Treatment Plan, based on your hopes for
therapy and what is realistic within the agreed time frame. CBT is a proactive
therapy so further sessions will involve you learning skills and strategies
alongside values based goal setting and problem solving.  You will be supported
in actively practising these skills between sessions ready for further
reflection and fine tuning when you return. CBT is all about coaching people to
become their own therapist, so towards the end of therapy we will develop a
plan for handling setbacks and promoting emotional resilience. My nursing
background enables me to offer an holistic approach to your difficulties,
taking into account physical health conditions and the role of medications
prescribed for mood management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;testimonials:36b7a485e343642b2e17a39b858818da&#34;&gt;Testimonials&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
Having suffered with OCD for 20 years I sought Cognitive Behavioural Therapy 
and Bridget came into my life as a blessing! She handled my situation with 
great care and empathy and used her extensive skills to teach me and guide me 
into dealing with my OCD and learning how to free myself from some of the 
debilitating symptoms that it causes. Bridget is professional and thorough and 
puts everything into helping you to heal yourself. She is compassionate yet 
tough when she knows that you need to be tough! She has given me tools &amp; 
skills that enabled me to get my life back. She is incredible! If you need 
her, go and see her, you will be so thankful you did!
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lucy, Worcestershire&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I want to thank you for the time that you have given to me over the last
months.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
This is the first time that I have needed professional help. When I first came
to you I could not envisage a positive outcome or a time when I would be able
to return to my old self.  However, thanks to your wise counsel,  vision,
support and teaching I now have many new skills developed during our CBT
sessions that I use daily. I  truly believe that I will not be returning to my
old self but in fact a new, better and more fulfilled self.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Bridget, my family and I are eternally grateful to you for our time together.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;June 2016&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About you</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About you and the problems you may be experiencing.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My training and experience is in working with people from 16 upwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cognitive Behavioural Therapy has been recommended in the NICE Guidelines, (The National Institute for Health and Clinical Excellence) for the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Depression&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Obsessive Compulsive Disorder (OCD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Panic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phobia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health Anxiety&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Anxiety&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generalised Anxiety Disorder or Excessive Worry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am experienced and trained in the individual evidence based protocols for each of these problems and this informs my practice. However, my experience of real people tells me that few people actually fit into these neat boxes and a broader or ‘transdiagnostic’ approach can be beneficial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a strong interest and considerable experience in the following areas
for which an ACT approach has been found to be particularly beneficial:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping people manage their emotions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing Stress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing long term conditions eg Chronic Fatigue or Multiple Sclerosis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building Self Acceptance  to boost Self Esteem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mood difficulties following bereavement of loved ones or pets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Binge Eating&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shyness or social difficulties relating to autistic spectrum disorder traits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coming to terms with change, for example, following divorce or retirement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also enjoy working with people who just need someone to help them step back,
take stock and reconnect with their values.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever your problem, your treatment plan will be tailor-made to suit your
individual needs. We will also have regular reviews to ensure skills and
strategies being learned and practised continue to fit with your planned hopes
for change.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/about-me/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;referrals:8723697e33f65823610bf3f676b8d742&#34;&gt;Referrals&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I accept referrals from: individuals, GPs, Employment Assistance Programmes,
and Insurance Providers (I am in the process of registering with these
organisations)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;current:8723697e33f65823610bf3f676b8d742&#34;&gt;Current&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been working within Adult Primary Care Mental Services for just over 10
years, completing my Postgraduate Qualification in CBT in 2010. I now share my
time between NHS based work and offering two days of Private Practice from the
Wellbeing Centre In Malvern, Worcestershire.  I work on Friday and Saturday
Mornings, seeing people from aged 16 upwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alongside my individual work with patients, I am a Clinical Supervisor within
the NHS and as an external Supervisor privately.  I am also involved with the
development and facilitation of group-work programmes, most recently devising
and delivering Acceptance and Commitment Therapy groups, within the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a continuing commitment to best practice and regularly attend workshops
and Courses which support my professional development and contribute to my
ongoing Accreditation and Registration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an Accredited member of the British Association of Behavioural and
Cognitive Therapists and the Nursing and Midwifery Council, my work is
underpinned by the Professional Standards of Conduct and Ethics outlined by
these established organisations. I am also a member of the Association for
Contextual and Behavioural Scientists, which enables me to develop my practice
within the ACT model. I receive regular Clinical Supervision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;qualifications:8723697e33f65823610bf3f676b8d742&#34;&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post Graduate Diploma in Cognitive and Behavioural Therapy, University Of Birmingham
2010&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diploma of Higher Education (Nursing) Part 13 of Register RMN (Distinction)
Pin No. 00E0415W, 2003&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor of Arts (Honours) Open University 1998&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;experience:8723697e33f65823610bf3f676b8d742&#34;&gt;Experience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2003: Following completion of my Mental Health Nursing Diploma, I worked on
an Acute Psychiatric Ward in Worcester, prior to moving to a Day Hospital
setting, where I worked with people individually and in groups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2006: Joined Primary Care Mental Health Service in Worcestershire as a
Gateway Worker (this involved, mental health reviews, using CBT approach
interventions and signposting for other Services).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With a growing interest in developing my therapy skills I completed the
Postgraduate Diploma in CBT at the University of Birmingham in 2008-10. I am
now in my 5th year as an Accredited member of the BABCP (British Association
for Cognitive and Behavioural Psychotherapists). I continue to work with
adults from 16 upwards within the NHS and privately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I&amp;rsquo;m not working or learning, I&amp;rsquo;m kept pretty busy with family, (I have 5
children, though 3 are grown up!), dogs, and garden. I also enjoy getting out
and about in our beautiful local countryside!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My commitment to you</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/my-commitment-to-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/my-commitment-to-you/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;professional-bodies:f261da53a66dd42998430d3eae0b2126&#34;&gt;Professional Bodies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will uphold the requirements of Accreditation by the British Association of
Cognitive and Behavioural Psychotherapists (BABCP) and Registration by the
Nursing and Midwifery Council (NMC). This requires my commitment to regular
attendance of ongoing professional development courses and accessing regular
Clinical Supervision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;confidentiality:f261da53a66dd42998430d3eae0b2126&#34;&gt;Confidentiality&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guarantee our sessions will remain strictly private and confidential in line
with the ethical standards of the BABCP.  The only  exception to this would be
if you tell me something that makes me very concerned about your safety or the
safety of someone else. In that case, I would have gained your agreement in the
first session to share my concerns with a designated family member or
Professional. This would usually be a step we would plan together to enable you
to access the further help you need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To improve my Service to you and as part of the requirements of my Professional
Body, I may review our sessions with my Clinical Supervisor. Your anonymity
will be maintained throughout and the Supervisor is also bound to keep your
information confidential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;data-storage:f261da53a66dd42998430d3eae0b2126&#34;&gt;Data Storage&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will store your data electronically and make use of two-factor authentication
for all services involved in storing your data. I am a registered Data
Controller under the Data Protection Act 1998 and I
operate in accordance with its legal requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;social-media-policy:f261da53a66dd42998430d3eae0b2126&#34;&gt;Social Media Policy&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the interests of maintaining the clear boundaries of a Professional
Therapeutic relationship, I do not instigate or accept links with my patients
on social media sites. Please do not take this personally!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;insurance:f261da53a66dd42998430d3eae0b2126&#34;&gt;Insurance&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hold Professional Insurance (professional indemnity and public liability).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful links</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/useful-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/useful-links/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;reading-material:d8ec52b657cacf2a3854c16d08966b53&#34;&gt;Reading material&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mind.org.uk/information-support/drugs-and-treatments/cognitive-behavioural-therapy-cbt/#.VttCEFuLSVM&#34;&gt;What is CBT
(MIND)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.actmindfully.com.au/free_resources&#34;&gt;ACT Mindfully&lt;/a&gt;. This is a
website from Russ Harris, the author of The Happniess Trap (a popular
self-help book). You can download the first 2 chapters of this book
for free.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;videos:d8ec52b657cacf2a3854c16d08966b53&#34;&gt;Videos&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C-ZuqeyxULM&#34;&gt;Headstuck! What is Experiential
Avoidance?&lt;/a&gt;. This short animation
provides a great introduction to some key concepts underlying Acceptance and
Commitment Therapy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://mrsmindfulness.com/what-is-mindfulness/&#34;&gt;An introduction to
Mindfulness&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 19:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk/contact/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for taking the time to read through these pages, if you think I may be
the right person to help you with your difficulties, please contact me now, to
arrange a brief informal chat at a mutually agreed time. This will give me a
broad understanding of what you want to work on and whether I can help. It will
also give you the opportunity to ask any questions and get a sense of whether
you feel we can work together before committing to your first appointment.
Feel free to call me, or if you prefer email me a summary of your current
problem and we can take it from there. You can also fill out the contact form
below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will endeavour to get back to you as soon as I can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phone: &lt;strong&gt;07752 199258&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:contact@bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk&#34;&gt;contact@bridgetmaddisoncbt.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe 
src=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1nHvkFc7cPkGPb0PiaDYbWHIcL-P60IiLBME4lXQ97ok/viewform?embedded=true&#34; 
width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;500&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; marginheight=&#34;0&#34; 
marginwidth=&#34;0&#34;&gt;Loading...&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ready to go ahead and make an appointment? Please feel free to contact the Centre for Wellbeing direct to book an appointment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Website:    &lt;a href=&#34;http://centreforwellbeing.co.uk/&#34;&gt;centreforwellbeing.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phone:     &lt;strong&gt;01684 574888&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Centre for Wellbeing&lt;br /&gt;
52 Malvern Road&lt;br /&gt;
Malvern&lt;br /&gt;
WR14 3PP&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fees:    £60 per Therapy hour (55 mins) Payment by cash, cheque, or Paypal&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;cancellations-or-non-attendance:3c4864f00d23f7ea35511ec930ce1d9c&#34;&gt;Cancellations or non attendance&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please to get in touch as soon as possible if you are unable to attend. For less than 24 hours notice I would ask you to pay 50% of the session fee.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>